The Eyes of My Mother is a drama, horror film directed by Nicolas Pesce.
A young, lonely woman is consumed by her deepest and darkest
desires after tragedy strikes her quiet country life.
Francisca, played by Kika Magalhães.
Mother, played by Diana Agostini.
Charlie, played by Will Brill.
Kimiko, played by Clara Wong.
Young Francisca, played by Olivia Bond.
Antonio, played by Joey Curtis-Green.
The Eyes of My Mother is a 2016 American black-and-white horror film written,
edited and directed by Nicolas Pesce in his directorial debut.
It stars Kika Magalhães, Olivia Bond, Diana Agostini, and Paul Nazak.
The film was produced by Borderline Presents and Tandem
Pictures and distributed by Magnet Releasing.
The Eyes of My Mother premiered at the 2016 Sundance Film Festival and was theatrically
released in the United States on December 2, 2016, by Magnet Releasing.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics
and a polarizing reception from audiences.
The film explores themes of death of father, dead body,
black and white, death of mother, horror.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.